# ABDUL SAMAD KHAN

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER



- 0336 0097019
- abdulsamad31650@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/abdul samad676
- www.github.com/AbdulSamad676/
- Gandali Essaki, Bannu

## SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- BOOTSTRAP 4/5
- TAILWIND CSS
- REACTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- ES6
- REACTJS
- REACT REDUX
- REACT-ROUTER

## **EDUCATION**

#### SSC

BISE Bannu 2013 - 2015

#### **HSSC**

BISE Bannu 2015 - 2017

#### **BS SOFTWARE ENGINEERING**

**UET Peshawar** 2017 - 2021

## LANGUAGES

**Pashto** native

Urdu

fluent **English** conversational

## **PROFILE**

A dedicated front-end developer with 1 Year experience. My journey in web programming has equipped me with a solid foundation in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript. Recently, I've delved into the exciting world of ReactJS, mastering its fundamentals and eager to apply my skills in dynamic web development. Currently seeking opportunities to contribute my skills as a ReactJS Developer for a forward-thinking company.

## **EXPERIENCES**

• Frontend Developer (freelancer) **FIVEER/ UPWORK** 

Sep,2022 - Present

 ReactJS Internee **NextPak Agile Solution** 

June-2022 - Sep2022

After Completing Basic Frontend at AWSOL I joined NextPak Agile Solutions as a ReactJS Internee to Learn advanced web technologies.

 Web Designer **AWSOL Lahore** 

Aug 2021 - May 2022

After graduation, I started my career as a web design internee and at Awsol then I get a job at Awsol as a web designer

 Solid Waste Management (FYP) **UET Peshawar (Mardan Campus)** June 2020 - Sep 2021

In my final year at university, I led the development of a Solid Waste Management System for WSSC Mardan as my Final Year Project.